<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ThousandthStar&#39;s blog</title>
    <link>https://thousandthstar.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ThousandthStar&#39;s blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 18:17:24 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://thousandthstar.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>8bit Duels Devlog Part 4</title>
      <link>https://thousandthstar.github.io/posts/8bd-part4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 18:17:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thousandthstar.github.io/posts/8bd-part4/</guid>
      <description>Hello! Welcome to the fourth part of my devlog where I develop my multiplayer turn-based game. I previously didn&amp;rsquo;t have a name, but I have decided to name it 8bit Duels! I think this fits the theme pretty nicely. Anyways, on with the devlog!
Refactoring This devlog is all about refactoring, and how I made my code cleaner. I did this by creating a workspace shared between the client and the server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8bit Duels Devlog Part 3</title>
      <link>https://thousandthstar.github.io/posts/8bd-part3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 18:15:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thousandthstar.github.io/posts/8bd-part3/</guid>
      <description>Hello Readers! Welcome to the third devlog on this series where I code a multiplayer turn-based strategy game! If you haven&amp;rsquo;t read the three previous posts, go check them out! This week, I created a simple and exciting selecting system for my troops. Without further ado, let&amp;rsquo;s get into it. Hope you enjoy!
Troop selecting In the last devlog, I talk about how I implemented the spawning mechanism in my game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8bit Duels Devlog Part 2</title>
      <link>https://thousandthstar.github.io/posts/8bd-part2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 18:12:30 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thousandthstar.github.io/posts/8bd-part2/</guid>
      <description>Hello readers! This is my progress for week 2 of coding my multiplayer game with Rust and Bevy. This post is a bit late, and should’ve been out yesterday, but I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to make it in time. Anyways, here is my progress this week. As a reminder, this is only a side project, and I don&amp;rsquo;t work on it for extended periods of time, so progress is slow.
In this post, we will cover three things:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8bit Duels Devlog Part 1</title>
      <link>https://thousandthstar.github.io/posts/8bd-part1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 18:07:54 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thousandthstar.github.io/posts/8bd-part1/</guid>
      <description>Hello readers! Welcome to the week 1 devlog of my multiplayer game using Rust and the Bevy game engine. In this post, I will talk about my progress for the first week. This isn&amp;rsquo;t the beginning of the project, but rather my first devlog. Without further ado, let&amp;rsquo;s get into it!
Please note that you are more than welcome to comment on my code. Hints on how to make it more efficient, performant, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8bit Duels Devlog Intro</title>
      <link>https://thousandthstar.github.io/posts/8bd-intro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2022 17:54:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thousandthstar.github.io/posts/8bd-intro/</guid>
      <description>Hello readers! This is a short post introducing my first blog series, where I will document my process creating a multiplayer turn-based game. The game is not named yet.
Below is what I&amp;rsquo;ll explore in this post: What I&amp;rsquo;m making: in this section, I&amp;rsquo;ll tell a bit more about what kind of game I&amp;rsquo;m making as well as what are my expectations and goals for this project.
Language and tools: I will cover the technology stack behind my game.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
